[{"answer": "You took woodshop", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I made a tie rack", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh yes", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I think it's still available", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Uh huh", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Nothing, I was just wondering what you were doing", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "There was no bingo, it came from outside", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Someone outside didn't get a bingo, someone outside yelled bingo you moron", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Here", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Is there enough room", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Pointing upwards Look..", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I would never marry anybody I didn't love", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Not acknowledging my friend's comment You'll be okay little fish", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " NO!, He's fine.  Fish are very resilient animals you know. Don't worry, I won't get another fish", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Hi my friend", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Sure, come in", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "My Dad gave my friend a ring", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You're such a retard, it was an engagement ring", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "So now you'll have a mother", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I do, she's real funny", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'm hemorrhaging", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " I don't want, I don't need your help...", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Why not", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " He's okay isn't he", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "He was allergic to bees", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " There were just too many of 'em", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Sure", "docId": "My-Girl.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Bye", "qsentId": 30}]